Long ago, our galaxy was ruled
很久以前，我们的银河系被统治
by an alien race called the Eridians
来自一个叫伊瑞德人的外星种族
whose power and technology
其力量和技术
were far beyond human comprehension.
远远超出了人类的理解范围。
Though they disappeared ages ago,
尽管它们很久以前就消失了，
they left behind fragments of their technology,
他们留下了一些技术碎片，
scraps that became the foundation
成为基础的废料
for all human advancement.
促进人类的进步。
But the Eridians' greatest secrets
但埃瑞德人最大的秘密
were hidden in a vault
藏在保险库里
located on the planet Pandora.
位于潘多拉星球。
The once peaceful world was overrun by corporations,
曾经和平的世界被企业占领，
criminals,
罪犯，
- and treasure seekers... -Guns, guns, guns!
- 和寻宝者... -枪，枪，枪！
...fighting and killing one another
互相争斗、互相残杀
for a chance to find the vault.
以获得找到保险库的机会。
But it remained hidden.
但它仍然隐藏着。
Then, amidst the clouds of chaos,
然后，在一片混乱之中，
a glimmer of hope shone through.
一线希望的光芒闪现。
A prophecy.
一个预言。
That one day,
那一天，
a daughter of Eridia would open the vault
埃里迪亚的女儿会打开保险库
and restore order to the broken planet.
并恢复这个破碎星球的秩序。
Yeah.
是的。
That sounds like some wacko B.S., right?
这听起来像是一些疯狂的废话，对吧？
Well, I thought so too, until...
嗯，我也这么认为，直到......
this mess happened.
发生了这样的混乱。
There he is!
他就在那儿！
Stop!
停止！
God damn!
该死的！
There's no air holes in there.
那里没有气孔。
What a stupid helmet.
真是一顶愚蠢的头盔。
Tina.
蒂娜.
Hey.
嘿。
I'm Roland.
我是罗兰。
Yeah. There's been some, uh...
是的。有一些，呃……
There's been some trouble.
出了一些麻烦。
And Atlas,
阿特拉斯
he sent me to bring you to safety.
他派我来带你到安全的地方。
- My dad sent you? - That's right.
- 我爸派你来的？ - 没错。
His shortest soldier?
他最矮的士兵是？
Yeah, his shortest soldier
是啊，他最矮的士兵
to save his least funny daughter.
去拯救他最不搞笑的女儿。
Code three security breach.
代码三安全漏洞。
The station is in lockdown.
该站处于封锁状态。
All personnel must shelter in place.
所有人员必须就地避难。
- Okay, let's go. - Hey, hey, hey!
- 好的，我们走吧。 - 嘿，嘿，嘿！
- Let's slow down. -Target in sight!
- 我们放慢速度。- 目标在望！
Come on. Come on.
来吧，来吧。
Stop!
停止！
Stay down!
趴下！
- Oh, God. - No, no!
- 噢，天啊。 - 不，不！
Catch.
抓住。
Fake stormtrooper-ass bitch.
假冲锋队员婊子。
Come here.
到这儿来。
Code three security breach.
代码三安全漏洞。
Come on. Come on.
来吧，来吧。
The station is now in lockdown.
该站目前已被封锁。
Wait, I changed my mind. Take me back to my cell.
等一下，我改变主意了。带我回牢房。
- Please. - Come on.
- 请你这样做。- 来吧。
Holy shit! One of the Psychos got out.
天啊！一个精神病患者逃出来了。
It's time to go insane!
是时候疯狂了！
You're in my spot.
你在我的位置上了。
Put him down. Put him down.
放他下来，放他下来。
Hey, easy.
嘿，简单。
What do you, uh...
你怎么了，呃…
What do you say me and you be friends?
你觉得我可以和你做朋友吗？
Shit.
拉屎。
Sorry, Knoxx.
抱歉，诺克斯。
My girl.
我的女孩。
Krieg, what's up, man?
克里格，发生什么事了，伙计？
You want some pancakes?
你想要一些煎饼吗？
My girl broken.
我的女孩心碎了。
It's Krieg, right?
是克里格吧？
Yeah.
是的。
What do you say you help me get her outta here?
你能帮我把她救出来吗？
Of course,
当然，
we can't all be the daughter of Eridia,
我们不可能都是埃利迪亚的女儿，
skipping down the path of destiny.
沿着命运的道路跳跃。
Some of us have to work for a living.
我们中的一些人必须工作来谋生。
You don't have to do this, you know.
你不必这么做，你知道。
I mean, I can pay you.
我的意思是，我可以付钱给你。
Yeah, whatever's in my wallet right now, it's yours.
是的，现在我钱包里的东西都是你的。
Okay?
好的？
Shut up or I'll break your other arm.
闭嘴，不然我就打断你的另一只胳膊。
Oh, no, one arm's good.
哦，不，一只手臂就好。
That's fine.
没关系。
-'Sup? - Sorry.
-怎么了？- 抱歉。
- Quinn. - Lilith.
- 奎因。 - 莉莉丝。
We do have other seats, you know.
你知道，我们确实还有其他座位。
Then he won't have any trouble finding one.
这样，他就可以轻松地找到它了。
Uh, not tonight.
呃，今晚不行。
Top shelf.
顶层架子。
Not sure how top you think the shelves are.
不确定您认为架子有多高。
Eh, buy your kid some dance lessons.
呃，给你的孩子买一些舞蹈课。
Hot date?
热门约会？
You remember that heist down in Lectra City last month?
你还记得上个月在莱克特拉城发生的抢劫案吗？
Yeah, a couple of guards died.
是的，有几名警卫死亡。
Yeah, well, this sad sack was the trigger man.
是啊，这个可悲的家伙就是枪手。
Listen, I never meant to shoot anyone.
听着，我从来没想过要射杀任何人。
I was...
我当时……
I'm getting too old for this shit.
我已经太老了，不适合做这种事。
Bounty hunting? Uh.
赏金猎人？呃。
It's for the young and stupid. Am I right?
这是给年轻和愚蠢的人准备的。我说得对吗？
You really want me to answer that?
你真的想让我回答这个问题吗？
I do not.
我没有。
Lilith.
莉莉丝。
Piss off.
滚开。
I heard you were quite the crusty old...
我听说你是个脾气暴躁的老头……
Wait. Wait, wait.
等一下。等一下，等一下。
We, uh, maybe got off on the wrong foot.
我们，呃，也许一开始就犯了错误。
You see, um...
你看，嗯...
I represent a very wealthy man
我代表一位非常富有的人
who has a contract for you.
谁有与你的合同。
I've got a job.
我有工作。
Maybe next month.
也许下个月吧。
You collect on that scum
你收集那些渣滓
dead or alive, right?
是死是活，对吗？
Hey.
嘿。
Not in here, big boy.
别在这里，大个子。
We don't want any trouble.
我们不想惹任何麻烦。
It's just, uh, our employer is, uh, not one for waiting.
只是，我们的雇主并不是一个喜欢等待的人。
Who is?
谁是？
Are you with these assholes?
你是跟这些混蛋一伙的吗？
Or are you just a fan of violence?
或者你只是暴力的爱好者？
These gentlemen work
这些先生们工作
or should I say "worked" for me?
或者我应该说对我“有用”？
I'll get Kimber to clean this up.
我会让金伯来清理这个。
Thanks, Quinn.
谢谢，奎因。
That was impressive.
这真是令人印象深刻。
I warned them not to underestimate you.
我警告他们不要低估你。
My name is Deukalian Atlas.
我的名字是 Deukalian Atlas。
And, uh...
还有，呃...
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
This is...
这是...
This is rather awkward.
这确实有些尴尬。
Hey, you there.
嘿，你在那儿。
Fat boy.
胖小子。
Put me on.
把我放上去。
But she just killed Frank and Wes.
但她刚刚杀了弗兰克和韦斯。
But she would never shoot a man of your caliber.
但她绝不会向你这样有实力的人开枪。
Mm.
毫米。
As I was saying...
正如我所说的……
Start walking.
开始行走。
My name is Deukalian Atlas.
我的名字是 Deukalian Atlas。
President of the...
总统...
The Atlas Corporation?
阿特拉斯公司？
Clue's in the name.
名字里有线索。
Look, uh, this has been a really long day.
瞧，呃，这真是漫长的一天。
Can we just skip to,
我们可以直接跳到
I don't know, whatever this is?
我不知道，这是什么？
Of course.
当然。
My daughter has been kidnapped,
我的女儿被绑架了，
and I need her returned to me.
我需要她回到我身边。
Bounty hunter, not babysitter.
赏金猎人，不是保姆。
Haven't you got some toy soldiers you can send?
您没有可以发送的玩具士兵吗？
Yes, the Crimson Lance.
是的，深红之枪。
Unfortunately, the kidnapper is one of them.
不幸的是，绑架者就是其中之一。
I need an outsider.
我需要一个局外人。
Someone who knows how to handle a planet
知道如何处理行星的人
full of Psychos, skags, and vault hunters
充满了精神病患者、混蛋和金库猎人
like they were born there.
就像他们出生在那里一样。
Your daughter's on Pandora?
你女儿在潘多拉上吗？
Thoughts and prayers.
思念和祈祷。
But you couldn't pay me enough
但你付给我的钱不够
to set foot on that shithole again.
再次踏上那片鬼地方。
Are you sure about that?
你确定吗？
Oh.
哦。
Maybe you could.
也许你可以。
Okay, I'll start when my current contract ends.
好的，我将在现有合同结束后开始工作。
Seems like you're free to start immediately.
看来您可以立即开始。
Give her the beacon.
把信标给她。
Activate this device when you find my daughter
当你找到我的女儿时激活这个装置
and my people will retrieve her.
我的人民将会把她救回来。
You haven't disappointed so far, Lilith.
到目前为止你还没有令我失望，莉莉丝。
I advise you not to start.
我劝你不要开始。
Sorry.
对不起。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Thank you for flying Atlas transport pods.
感谢您驾驶 Atlas 运输舱。
You've arrived at your destination.
您已抵达目的地。
Pandora.
潘多拉。
Let me tell you everything you need to know
让我告诉你你需要知道的一切
about Pandora.
关于潘多拉。
It's a shithole.
这简直就是个粪坑。
I should know. I'm from here.
我应该知道。我来自这里。
God, I hate this planet.
天哪，我讨厌这个星球。
It's the kind of place
这是一个地方
you don't ever wanna return to.
你永远不想再回去。
So, the sooner I find the girl,
所以，我越早找到那个女孩，
the sooner I can get the hell outta here.
我就能越快离开这里。
The soldier had hijacked one of Atlas' shuttles
这名士兵劫持了阿特拉斯的一架航天飞机
and crash-landed here months ago.
几个月前就坠毁在这里。
There wasn't much left of it.
剩下的不多了。
It'd been stripped for parts
它被拆成几部分
and vandalized by vault hunters.
并遭到金库猎人的破坏。
No way to know if he and Tina even survived.
根本不知道他和蒂娜是否还活着。
Wanna know if you've seen her.
想知道你是否见过她。
But then I spoke to some locals.
但后来我和一些当地人交谈过。
Scavenger kids barely scraping out a living.
拾荒儿童勉强维持生计。
They told me Tina and the soldier
他们告诉我蒂娜和士兵
had passed through weeks ago
几周前就已经通过
heading north towards Fyrestone.
向北朝 Fyrestone 行驶。
Then I ran into some other locals.
然后我遇到了一些其他当地人。
Run!
跑步！
Psychos. Murderous gangs.
精神病患者、凶残的团伙。
It was time to catch a ride and head north.
是时候搭车向北走了。
Hello, vault hunter.
你好，秘藏猎人。
Need a ride?
需要搭车吗？
Yeah, I'm not a vault hunter, but...
是的，我不是一名秘藏猎人，但是......
Then welcome aboard.
欢迎加入。
People inside, bags up top.
里面有人，上面有袋子。
Don't need any explosives going pop.
不需要任何炸药爆炸。
That is a mess to clean up, believe me.
相信我，那真是太糟糕了。
Hello, passenger.
您好，乘客。
My name is Marcus.
我叫马库斯。
But of course,
当然，
you're not here for small talk.
你来这里不是为了闲聊的。
You are here to find the vault.
你来这里是为了寻找保险库。
Uh, you can stop there.
呃，你可以停在那里。
Not a vault hunter.
不是秘藏猎人。
Just need a ride.
只需要搭车。
If you say so.
如果你这么说的话。
Well, hello, brave vault hunter.
你好，勇敢的秘藏猎人。
So, you've come in search
所以，你来这里是为了寻找
of the secret lost vault of the Eridians,
伊瑞德人失落的秘密宝库，
right here on Pandora!
就在潘多拉这里！
Do you want to be rich beyond your wildest dreams?
您想变得富有到超乎想像吗？
First, you must find the keys,
首先，你必须找到钥匙，
then the vault itself, but it won't be easy.
然后是保险库本身，但这并不容易。
Could you turn this shit off?
你能把这个狗屎关掉吗？
Not a vault hunter.
不是秘藏猎人。
No can do.
没有办法。
This bus is for transporting vault hunters, so...
这辆巴士是用来运送金库猎人的，所以……
Will you be the one to find the vault?
您会是找到保险库的人吗？
Ancient alien treasure filled with high-tech secrets...
充满高科技秘密的古代外星宝藏......
Pandora is a dangerous place,
潘多拉是一个危险的地方，
so you need superior firepower.
所以你需要更强大的火力。
Prepare yourself with one of Marcus' munitions.
准备好马库斯的一枚弹药。
Next stop, Fyrestone,
下一站，Fyrestone，
where all vault hunters begin.
所有秘藏猎人的起点。
Uh, no.
呃，不。
Really, I am not...
真的，我不是...
Thanks.
谢谢。
Good luck, vault hunter.
祝你好运，秘藏猎人。
I hope you find what you're searching for.
我希望你能找到你在寻找的东西。
Two weeks on the trail,
经过两周的跋涉，
and it was as cold as Pandora's moons.
天气如潘多拉的卫星一样寒冷。
Tina and the soldier were long gone.
蒂娜和士兵早已不见踪影。
I needed a miracle, but I got something else.
我需要一个奇迹，但我得到的却是别的。
My eye!
我的眼睛！
You shot me in my eye!
你射中了我的眼睛！
You blinded me for life!
你让我失去了生命的意义！
How will I manage to survive?
我该如何生存下去？
I'm just kidding!
我只是在开玩笑！
I was designed to withstand all kinds of violent acts,
我被设计来抵御各种暴力行为，
even completely unjustified ones like yours.
甚至像你这样的完全不合理的。
Now, I bet you're wondering,
现在，我猜你一定想知道，
what's the deal with this thing?
这是怎么回事？
Uh, no, I'm not.
呃，不，我不是这样的。
I'm programmed for humor,
我天生幽默，
so I will process that as "witty banter."
所以我会将其理解为“诙谐的玩笑。”
Beat it.
打败它。
I'm a Hyperion brand CL4P-TP,
我是 Hyperion 品牌 CL4P-TP，
possibly the last of my kind still in service.
可能是我这个种族中最后一个仍在服役的人了。
But you can call me...
但你可以叫我...
Whoopsie! Ha!
哎呀！哈！
You accidentally shot me in the face again.
你又不小心射到我的脸上了。
As I was saying, you can call me Claptrap.
正如我所说，你可以叫我 Claptrap。
You know, I can do this all night,
你知道，我可以整晚这样做，
so piss off.
所以滚开。
Believe me, I wish I could
相信我，我希望我能
based on what little I've experienced
根据我所经历的一点点
of your horrendous personality.
你的可怕个性。
But I have no choice.
但我别无选择。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Did Atlas send you?
是 Atlas 派你来的吗？
Atlas? Yuck!
阿特拉斯？真恶心！
I don't work for the competition.
我不为竞争对手工作。
No, I've been lying dormant under a garbage heap
不，我一直躺在垃圾堆下
for... calculating... 36 years!
算起来...是...36年！
But the moment you landed on Pandora,
但当你踏上潘多拉星球的那一刻，
I was reactivated
我被重新激活了
because I've been programmed to help you upon your return!
因为我已经被编程来在你回来时帮助你！
No one knew I was coming here.
没有人知道我要来这里。
Not even me.
就连我也没有。
Who programmed you?
谁给你编程了？
I don't know!
我不知道！
Which is a shame, because you're an awful person
这很可惜，因为你是个糟糕的人
and I'd love to know who to blame for this.
我很想知道这事该怪谁。
Since I don't, I have no choice but to serve you
既然我没有，我别无选择，只能为你服务
until you're dead.
直到你死去。
Did that sound like a threat? Sorry.
这听起来像是威胁吗？抱歉。
Anyway, as long as you're not dead,
反正只要你还没死，
- I'm here to help. - Oh.
- 我来帮忙。 - 哦
And I have many skills.
而且我有很多技能。
Balancing.
平衡。
Turning in circles.
转圈圈。
I don't need a partner.
我不需要伴侣。
Uh, I can also access the ECHOnet.
呃，我也可以访问 ECHOnet。
Did you say "ECHOnet"?
您说的是“ECHOnet”吗？
Can you use it to find someone?
你能用它找人吗？
Of course. Just show me a picture.
当然。只要给我看一张照片就行。
I'll hack and search
我会入侵并搜索
its slowly dying visual banks for matches
它的火柴视觉库正在慢慢消亡
and find your target's last known location.
并找到目标的最后已知位置。
Find her.
找到她。
She was last seen outside Fyrestone.
她最后一次出现是在 Fyrestone 外面。
Accessing network.
正在访问网络。
♪ Scanning, scanning Scanning ♪
♪ 扫瞄，扫瞄，扫瞄 ♪
Could you do it without the singing?
不唱歌你能做到吗？
Yes!
是的！
♪ Scanning, scanning Scanning ♪
♪ 扫瞄，扫瞄，扫瞄 ♪
Done!
完毕！
Your target was last recorded
您的目标上次被记录
near an abandoned quarry in the Tundra Express!
靠近苔原快车上的一个废弃采石场！
It's only 132 days on foot
步行只需132天
with a 98% chance of being eaten by a Craw maggot!
有 98% 的几率被 Craw 蛆虫吃掉！
I like those odds!
我喜欢这些几率！
We're gonna need some wheels.
我们需要一些轮子。
That's the Crimson Lance, Atlas' private army.
那是红色长矛，阿特拉斯的私人军队。
What are they doing here?
他们在这里干什么？
Oh, just a guess here.
哦，只是猜测。
Exactly the same thing you're doing.
和你做的一模一样。
And the Lance teaming up with the Psychos?
兰斯 (Lance) 和 Psychos 联手了吗？
It seems like Atlas will hire
看来 Atlas 会聘请
just about anyone to find his daughter.
几乎每个人都找到了他的女儿。
Concentrating. Sorry.
正在集中注意力。抱歉。
Huh. The Lance are leaving.
嗯。兰斯一家要走了。
I guess they didn't find her.
我猜他们没有找到她。
No more Mommy!
没有妈妈了！
Free lunch! Hot delivery!
免费午餐！热卖中！
Huh?
嗯？
That was so out of character to save those children.
拯救这些孩子的行为太不合常理了。
Well, I needed a ride.
好吧，我需要搭车。
For a second there,
有一瞬间，
I thought you weren't a horrible person.
我以为你不是一个可怕的人。
Phew! The world makes sense again.
呼！世界又恢复正常了。
Now, there's only room for one up front,
现在前面只剩下一个位置了，
but worry not.
但不用担心。
I can sit on your lap.
我可以坐在你的腿上。
Lilith!
莉莉丝！
You accidentally locked me in the back!
你不小心把我锁在后面了！
Please drain my battery.
请耗尽我的电池。
Put me back to sleep.
让我回去睡觉。
I won't tell.
我不会说的。
You said you wanted to help.
你说过你想帮忙。
I said I'm programmed to help.
我说我被设计来帮忙。
What I want to do is wipe my memory,
我想要做的是抹去我的记忆，
you horrendous she-devil.
你这个可怕的女魔头。
Are you sure these are the right coordinates?
您确定这些是正确的坐标吗？
Yes. This is the last known location of your quarry.
是的。这是你猎物的最后已知位置。
Get it?
得到它？
But it looks like she's long gone by now.
但看起来她现在已经走了很久了。
Does it?
是吗？
You know, it's quite a menagerie you've got here.
你知道，这里有着相当多的动物园。
You could start your own Pandoran zoo.
您可以建立自己的潘多拉动物园。
You must be Tina.
你一定是蒂娜。
Name's Lilith.
名字叫莉莉丝。
So, that soldier...
那么，那个士兵……
who brought you here,
谁带你来这里，
is he playing hide-and-seek, too?
他也在玩捉迷藏吗？
He left me.
他离开了我。
I haven't seen him in days.
我好几天没见到他了。
Well, I'm here to take you home
好吧，我来接你回家
to your father.
给你的父亲。
Yeah, he seems like a real, uh, sweetheart.
是的，他看起来真是一个可爱的人。
What? My daddy?
啥？我爸爸？
I get to see my daddy?
我能见到我的爸爸吗？
Really?
真的吗？
I've been so afraid.
我一直很害怕。
- Yeah. -I've been scared.
- 是啊。- 我很害怕。
Speaking of your daddy...
说到你的爸爸……
The noises outside really freaked me out.
外面的响声确实把我吓坏了。
I've just gotta let him know that I got you safe...
我只是想让他知道我保证你安全……
I should probably get my stuff.
我应该去拿我的东西了。
Shit.
拉屎。
I really love my daddy.
我真的爱我的爸爸。
He's such a nurturing parental figure.
他是一位如此富有爱心的父母形象。
Sure, I'll have to take your word for it.
当然，我必须相信你的话。
Miss Lilith,
莉莉丝小姐，
can you grab my Badonkadonk?
你能抓住我的 Badonkadonk 吗？
Your what now?
你现在什么？
You little...
你这个小...
I love it when bounty hunters drop by.
我很喜欢赏金猎人的来访。
Time to make it rain...
是时候下雨了……
with your body parts.
用你的身体部位。
Hey.
嘿。
You still alive down there?
你还活在下面吗？
She seems deranged.
她看上去精神错乱了。
You two have a lot in common.
你们俩有很多共同点。
Only she's smaller, nicer, cuter.
只是她更小、更漂亮、更可爱。
Hope that wasn't something important.
希望那不是什么重要的事情。
Fix this.
修复此问题。
Because, whoo, it's toast.
因为，哇，它完蛋了。
Where'd you go?
你去哪了？
Tina.
蒂娜.
Look, I... I'm here to save you.
看，我......我来救你了。
Do I look like I need saving?
我看上去像是需要拯救的样子吗？
'Cause I'm up here
因为我在这里
and you're all hiding under a car.
你们都躲在车底下。
Like a bitch!
像个母狗！
You get down here right now.
你现在就下来。
Oh, Krieg!
哦，战争！
This fancy-ass woman
这个花哨的女人
just pointed a gun at your best friend.
刚刚用枪指着你最好的朋友。
I will lick your spine clean.
我会舔干净你的脊椎。
Holed up with Psychos?
和精神病患者一起躲起来了吗？
He only used to be a Psycho.
他只是曾经是一个精神病患者。
Now he's my big brother!
现在他是我的哥哥！
How sweet.
多么甜蜜啊。
One of you kill the other, I'm gonna go get a coffee.
你们其中一个人杀了另一个人，我要去喝杯咖啡。
Tell her what she's won, Krieg.
告诉她她赢得了什么，克里格。
You've walked the wrong dog.
你遛错了狗。
Shoot him in the face.
朝他的脸开枪。
Shoot him in the face again.
再次朝他的脸开枪。
It's not working. Forget it. Abort. Go!
它不起作用。忘掉它。放弃。走吧！
Run, run!
快跑！快跑！
Mine's bigger.
我的更大一些。
Listen.
听。
I was sent by your father.
我是你父亲派来的。
Well, that's strange.
嗯，这很奇怪。
Because I don't have a father, lady.
因为女士，我没有父亲。
I know this planet can mess with your mind.
我知道这个星球可能会扰乱你的思绪。
My mind is awesome.
我的思维很奇妙。
My mind's so cool.
我的头脑太酷了。
Listen, I don't wanna be here. Nothing personal.
听着，我不想待在这里。没什么私人恩怨。
So, if you could just come with me,
所以如果你能跟我一起去
and you could talk to your dad
你可以和你爸爸谈谈
and you guys can sort it out,
你们可以解决这个问题，
family style. And I can...
家庭风格。而且我可以……
Nice work, lady. You led 'em straight to me.
干得好，女士。你直接把他们引向了我。
So, Atlas sent someone new to find the girl.
于是，阿特拉斯派了新的人去寻找这个女孩。
Never would have thought it was a scumbag vault hunter.
从来没想到这是一个卑鄙的金库猎人。
Actually, I'm not a scumbag vault hunter.
实际上，我并不是一个卑鄙的金库猎人。
Actually, she's a scumbag bounty hunter.
事实上，她是个卑鄙的赏金猎人。
You know, it's not my fault you suck at your job,
你知道，你工作不顺不是我的错，
whoever you are. Who are you?
无论你是谁。你是谁？
Commander Knoxx of the Crimson Lance.
深红之枪的指挥官诺克斯。
And I'm taking the girl with me.
我要带着这个女孩一起走。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是吗？
You and what army?
你和哪支军队？
The one right behind me.
就在我身后那个。
Move, move.
动起来，动起来。
Charlie team, right side.
查理队，右侧。
On your lead, with me!
跟着你，跟着我！
Stay behind me.
跟在我身后。
- I'll go. - Wait.
- 我去。 - 等一下。
And if you're both nice,
如果你们都很友善，
I'll put in a good word with Daddy.
我要向爸爸说几句好话。
Sounds good to me.
我觉得听起来不错。
Sergeant Russo,
鲁索中士，
bring me a neurocollar for the girl.
给我给那女孩拿来一个神经项圈。
Copy that, Commander.
收到，指挥官。
A collar?
领子？
I love new jewelry.
我喜欢新珠宝。
Yeah, I got you a gift, too.
是的，我也给你买了一份礼物。
Catch.
抓住。
Will you be my friend?
你愿意做我的朋友吗？
Oh, shit!
妈的！
Yes!
是的！
- Come on! - Hey!
- 来吧！ - 嘿！
Oh, shit!
妈的！
Tina!
蒂娜！
Stop. She's coming with me.
停下来。她要跟我一起去。
I leave you alone for 10 minutes...
我让你独自一人待10分钟......
Get in the car.
上车。
It's okay. He's with me.
没关系，他和我在一起。
I wish I wasn't.
我希望我不是这样。
Get in the car!
上车！
Go, go!
走吧，走吧！
Lilith, wait for me!
莉莉丝，等等我！
What did I tell you?
我告诉你什么了？
Minimal explosions.
最小爆炸。
No, I said no explosions!
不，我说了不要爆炸！
Who the hell are you?
你到底是谁？
This is Lilith. My dad sent her.
这是莉莉丝。是我爸爸派她来的。
Oh. She's a scumbag bounty hunter.
哦。她是个卑鄙的赏金猎人。
No, I am a high-end bounty hunter, pal.
不，我是一名高级赏金猎人，朋友。
-No. - And letting kids get shot at
-不 -而且让孩子们挨枪子
was not part of my job description.
不属于我的工作职责。
Oh, I bet it wasn't.
噢，我敢打赌不是这样的。
Lilith. Lilith.
莉莉丝。莉莉丝。
You inadvertently left your best friend behind!
你不经意间把你最好的朋友落下了！
To die!
去死吧！
Lilith!
莉莉丝！
Move, move, move!
动起来，动起来，动起来！
Hey! No pressure or anything
嘿！别有压力
but I'd love to come inside,
但我很想进来，
- if you get a chance. - What are you doing?
- 如果你有机会的话。- 你在做什么？
Just hoping you can reach out and scoop me up.
我只是希望你能伸出手来，把我抱起来。
You don't have to stop, just...
你不必停下来，只是...
Hey!
嘿！
Go easy on the merchandise.
对商品要宽容一些。
Here they come!
他们来了！
All units, you are now weapons free!
所有部队，现在你们可以自由使用武器了！
Take them down!
把他们拿下！
Damn it! You know what?
该死！你知道吗？
You drive.
你开车。
You programmed to steer?
你被编程来掌舵吗？
Who, me?
谁？我？
Who's driving the damn truck?
谁在驾驶这辆该死的卡车？
♪ Driving, driving, driving ♪
♪ 开车，开车，开车 ♪
♪ I'm so good at driving ♪
♪ 我开车技术真好 ♪
♪ I'm a robot driver ♪
♪ 我是一名机器人司机 ♪
Locking on target, ma'am.
锁定目标，女士。
We got a problem!
我们遇到问题了！
Brace for impact!
做好冲击的准备！
Holy underwear!
神圣的内衣！
I told you to drive. Damn it.
我让你开车的。该死。
Bandit one, four, up on the right. Cut 'em off.
土匪一号，四号，在右边。切断他们。
They got us pinned.
他们把我们困住了。
Not yet they don't. Hold on.
还没有。稍等一下。
- Brace yourselves. -What are you doing?
— 做好准备。— 你在做什么？
That was a terrible idea
那是个糟糕的想法
but it worked.
但它确实起作用了。
Mm, maybe.
嗯，也许吧。
Where are we?
我们在哪里？
Pisswash gully.
冲沟小沟。
What's that smell? Ugh.
那是什么味道？呃。
- Put the window up. - Why?
- 把窗户关上。 - 为什么？
Put the window up!
把窗户打开！
What is that smell?
那是什么味道？
What is this "smell" thing everyone talks about?
大家谈论的“气味”到底是什么？
- Listen to what I just said! - I don't want to!
- 听听我刚才说的话！ - 我不想！
- Roll the window up! - Don't tell me what to...
- 把窗户摇上来！ - 不要告诉我该怎么做……
It's in my mouth!
它就在我的嘴里！
Sardine showers.
沙丁鱼雨。
It's pee. It's pee.
这是尿。这是尿。
Now I got pee all in the middle of my truck.
现在我把尿都洒在卡车中间了。
Correction. It's 67% urine...
更正一下。67% 是尿液……
14% fecal...
14% 粪便...
- Oh! -Look out!
—哦！—小心！
Oh, God!
噢，天哪！
Don't nobody move.
谁也别动。
I'm not about to die in this...
我并不想就此死去……
Shut up.
住口。
Okay.
好的。
Is that...
那是……
This don't look so good.
这看上去不太好。
Yes, it is.
是的。
That thing looks angry!
那东西看起来很生气！
- Do you wanna press reverse? -Or hungry.
- 你想按倒车键吗？ - 或者饿了。
Oh, my God. It's gonna kill us. It's gonna kill us.
噢，天啊。这会要了我们的命。这会要了我们的命。
Wait a second.
等一下。
Do you want me to press reverse?
您要我按“反向”键吗？
No, I don't want you to do nothing!
不，我不想你什么都不做！
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
Your friends are back.
你的朋友们回来了。
Roland, don't be stupid.
罗兰，别傻了。
Just give us the girl.
只要把女孩给我们就行了。
Everybody, buckle up. I got a plan.
大家系好安全带。我有一个计划。
Somebody hold me!
谁来抱抱我！
Seriously, I have no seat belt!
说真的，我没有系安全带！
Roland, what are you doing?
罗兰，你在做什么？
- Go, go, go! -Hold on!
— 快走，快走，快走！— 坚持住！
- Hold it! -No, no, no!
- 稍等！- 不，不，不！
Shit.
拉屎。
Feels like we blew a tire.
感觉就像我们爆胎了。
You call that a plan?
你把这称为计划吗？
It worked, didn't it?
它成功了，不是吗？
Feel free to applaud.
请随意鼓掌。
Yay for not dying!
耶，没死！
Nothing.
没有什么。
- You stay here and keep watch. -Okay.
- 你留在这里守望。- 好的。
But it's you they don't seem to trust.
但他们似乎不信任你。
And who can blame them?
谁又能责怪他们呢？
♪ Scanning, scanning, scanning Scanning ♪
♪ 扫瞄，扫瞄，扫瞄 扫瞄 ♪
They should be after us by now.
他们现在应该正在追我们​​。
Stingrays won't pursue without ground support.
如果没有地面支援，黄貂鱼就不会进行追击。
Knoxx'll wait on reinforcements.
诺克斯将等待增援。
Let it down, big guy.
放下吧，大个子。
Before you added kidnapping to your resume
在你把绑架写进简历之前
you were an officer in Crimson Lance.
您是 Crimson Lance 的一名军官。
Right?
正确的？
Roland didn't kidnap me. He saved me.
罗兰没有绑架我。他救了我。
Saved you from what?
救了你什么？
A life of ease and plenty?
轻松富足的生活？
My daddy thinks I'm the daughter of Eridia.
我爸爸以为我是埃利迪亚的女儿。
I can open the vault.
我可以打开保险库。
The vault?
金库？
That's what this shit is about?
这就是这件事的来龙​​去脉？
You stole her for yourself.
你把她偷走了。
Now, do you know how many people have died
现在你知道死了多少人吗
looking for that hole in the dirt?
正在寻找泥土中的那个洞吗？
Well, I do.
嗯，我知道。
My mother was one of them.
我的母亲就是其中之一。
We have something they don't, baby girl.
我们拥有他们没有的东西，宝贝女儿。
Oh, let me guess. What? Spirit?
哦，让我猜猜。什么？精神？
Can-do attitude? The power of friendship?
敢做敢为的态度？友谊的力量？
A conscience.
有良心。
Whatever's in that vault,
无论保险库里有什么，
a man like Atlas can never get his hands on it.
像阿特拉斯这样的人永远也无法得到它。
- All right, Roland, calm down. -No!
- 好吧，罗兰，冷静下来。- 不！
She's a scumbag bounty hunter who works for Atlas.
她是一名为阿特拉斯工作的卑鄙赏金猎人。
What, and you think your band of merry heroes can stop him?
怎么，你认为你的快乐英雄团队可以阻止他吗？
Oh, we can try.
哦，我们可以试试。
We just can't watch our backs while doing it.
我们在做这件事的时候不能小心谨慎。
So, do me a favor. Take your weapon.
所以，帮我个忙。拿起你的武器。
Toss it over here.
把它扔过来。
Grab some supplies, take a walk.
拿上一些补给，出去走走。
You know, when Atlas finds out about that party back there,
你知道，当阿特拉斯发现那里有派对时，
I'm as good as dead.
我已经跟死了一样。
So, like it or not...
所以，不管喜欢与否...
we're on the same side.
我们是站在同一边的。
A side without an army, I might add.
我想补充的是，这是一支没有军队的一方。
So, I hope you got a better plan than
所以我希望你有一个比
driving down a thresher's gullet.
驶入脱粒机的咽喉。
No.
不。
But I know someone who does.
但我知道有人这么做。
A scientist, a vault expert.
一位科学家、一位保险库专家。
It was her idea to break Tina out and collect the keys.
救出蒂娜并拿回钥匙是她的主意。
One key down, two more to go.
按下一个键，还剩两个键。
And, of course, me.
当然还有我。
Load up.
加载。
Next stop, Sanctuary City.
下一站，庇护之城。
All right!
好的！
Road trip!
公路旅行！
All right, mask up.
好的，戴上面具。
We wanna keep a low profile.
我们想保持低调。
Market clear.
市场清淡。
Copy that.
复制一下。
Oh, this place sure has changed,
哦，这个地方确实变了，
for the worse.
变得更糟。
Back off. Back off! Heading to Gate 23.
后退。后退！ 前往 23 号登机口。
Oh, my.
噢，我的天。
Who's this handsome devil?
这位帅气的魔鬼是谁？
He's a badass killer.
他是一个恶毒的杀手。
And the reward's just gone up to 150 grand.
悬赏金额刚刚涨到 15 万美元。
Looks like you're not
看起来你不是
the only one that's special, kid.
唯一特别的一个，孩子。
Cannibal frog convention!
食人蛙大会！
Okay, so we're here.
好的，我们到了。
Now what?
现在该怎么办？
I need to locate my contact.
我需要找到我的联系人。
Moxxi will know how to find her.
莫西会知道如何找到她。
Moxxi?
莫西？
Yeah. You know her?
是的。你认识她吗？
Yeah, kind of.
是的，有点。
I mean, it's been a while.
我的意思是，已经有一段时间了。
Would you be a doll and hold this? Thank you.
你能变成一个洋娃娃并抱着它吗？谢谢。
Kriegy! Give me a ride.
克里吉！载我一程。
Hey.
嘿。
We're trying to stay low-key.
我们尽力保持低调。
Hey. Did you find
嘿。你找到了吗
what you were looking for in Fyrestone?
您在 Fyrestone 中寻找什么？
Never seen you before, stranger.
从未见过你，陌生人。
Nice try, Miss Vladof Infinity.
很好的尝试，Vladof Infinity 小姐。
I never forget a gun.
我永远不会忘记枪。
What are you up to now, Not-A-Vault-Hunter?
你现在在做什么呢，非秘藏猎人？
She's vault hunting.
她正在寻找金库。
I knew it.
我就知道。
I told you, I knew it.
我告诉过你，我知道。
Well, well, well.
好，好，好。
Look what the skag dragged in.
看看那条 skag 拖了什么东西进来。
-Hey, Mox. - Get on in there.
—嘿，莫克斯。—快进来吧。
Oh, you are most welcome.
哦，不用客气。
Milkshake for my little sugarplum,
为我的小甜心准备的奶昔，
and drinks for my friends.
还给我的朋友们喝了点酒。
I got something to show you.
我有东西要给你看。
Everyone, come over here.
大家快过来。
Step into my office.
走进我的办公室。
Roland?
罗兰？
- Roland. -I got it.
—罗兰。—我明白了。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
I knew it was you.
我知道是你。
- Oh, my God. -Hey, Larry.
- 噢，天哪。- 嘿，拉里。
You probably don't remember me, but
你可能不记得我了，但是
I sure remember you.
我当然记得你。
Your mama was a good woman.
你的妈妈是一位好女人。
Yeah, well, wouldn't know.
是啊，嗯，不知道。
All right. So, where is this, uh, scientist?
好的。那么，这位呃科学家在哪里？
So, this is where you're headed.
所以，这就是你要去的地方。
You go all the way up those stairs
你一路走上楼梯
and right there is the elevator.
电梯就在那里。
-Mm-hm. - Push the button.
-嗯哼。-按下按钮。
Passcode's "ECHO."
Passcode 的“ECHO”。
- ECHO? - ECHO.
- 回声？ - 回声。
You sure it's safe to stay there?
你确定呆在那里安全吗？
Yeah, as long as this one here don't blow up the joint.
是的，只要这个人不炸毁这个地方就行。
How's that milkshake there, sugar pie?
那边的奶昔怎么样，亲爱的？
Listen.
听。
For whatever it's worth...
无论它值多少钱……
I'm real happy that you came back home.
我真的很高兴你回家了。
And I hope that you know how much your mama loved you.
我希望你知道你的妈妈有多爱你。
She always told me how special you were.
她总是告诉我你有多特别。
You know, I appreciate the help.
你知道，我很感谢你的帮助。
Let's just leave it at that.
我们就到此为止吧。
Right.
正确的。
When they were chasing you, I was like,
当他们追你的时候，我当时想，
"Hey, don't shoot that guy. He's my roomie."
“嘿，别开枪打死那家伙。他是我的室友。”
- You... You said that? - Yeah, man.
- 你...你这么说？ - 是啊，哥们。
Hey, you see your bounty went up?
嘿，你看到你的赏金增加了吗？
- My? - Your bounty.
- 我的？- 你的赏金。
Get outta here.
离开这里。
Knoxx is on the warpath, stud.
诺克斯正在战斗，伙计。
What'd you do to her, man?
你对她做了什么？老兄？
Man, I kind of... kind of ghosted her, you know?
哥们，我有点……有点对她失去理智了，你知道吗？
Yeah, you did, man. You ghosted all of us, man.
是的，你确实这么做了，老兄。你对我们所有人都视而不见，老兄。
Yeah.
是的。
Anyway, man, it was really good to see you.
不管怎样，老兄，见到你真是太好了。
And, you know, you can trust me.
而且你知道，你可以相信我。
We're friends, man. I'm not gonna tell a soul.
我们是朋友，哥们。我不会告诉任何人的。
Oh, Larry, I'm not worried about you.
哦，拉里，我不担心你。
You're my guy.
你是我的男人。
You're my main man.
你是我的主男友。
I got a feeling you're not going to tell anybody.
我有种感觉，你不会告诉任何人。
Is he going to be okay?
他会没事吗？
Well, he'll have a hell of a hangover.
嗯，他肯定会宿醉得很厉害。
Ooh, who knew electricity provoked defecation?
噢，谁知道电能引发排便？
Hey.
嘿。
Y'all better hustle out the back.
你们最好赶紧从后门出去。
Go out this way.
往这边出去。
I got these guys. Go on. Go on.
我搞定了这些家伙。快走。快走。
- Claptrap, let's go. - Go on. Go on. Go on.
- 克拉普特拉普，我们走吧。- 继续走。继续走。继续走。
Your buddy boy here just drank about 10 shots too many
你的朋友刚刚喝了大约 10 杯
then he dropped like a sack of potatoes.
然后他像一袋土豆一样倒下了。
I think you forgot me.
我想你忘记我了。
Mm. And a tip is always appreciated.
嗯。如果能得到小费就更好了。
All right.
好的。
This looks like it.
看起来就是这样。
ECHO.
回声。
ECHO?
回声？
Sure that's the password?
确定这就是密码吗？
Maybe you gotta echo the "ECHO."
也许你应该回应“ECHO”。
ECHO. ECHO.
回声。回声。
All right.
好的。
You fools would literally be dead without me.
如果没有我，你们这些傻瓜就真的会死。
- You need me. -Here we go.
- 你需要我。- 开始吧。
Come on, Claptrap.
来吧，Claptrap。
Where are we going? Up.
我们要去哪儿？上去。
So, you trust this woman?
那么，你相信这个女人吗？
She's a xeno-archaeologist, all right?
她是一名外星考古学家，对吗？
She's a little odd.
她有点奇怪。
But she knows everything about the vault.
但她对保险库的一切了如指掌。
So, if she says something weird,
所以，如果她说了什么奇怪的话，
don't let it get to you, okay?
别让它影响到你，好吗？
I am 10 to the 100th power
我是10的100次方
impressed with this place.
对这个地方印象深刻。
Cool.
凉爽的。
Oh! I see you have the girl.
噢！我看你找到那个女孩了。
That's right.
这是正确的。
Did you find a vault key, too?
你也找到保险库钥匙了吗？
Hi, I'm Tina.
你好，我是蒂娜。
The special one.
很特别的一个。
Huh.
嗯。
Tannis.
坦尼斯。
Oh.
哦。
Hello, Lilith.
你好，莉莉丝。
Okay, good. So you guys know each other.
好的，很好。所以你们彼此认识。
Unfortunately.
很遗憾。
I'm not staying here.
我不留在这里。
What?
什么？
Okay.
好的。
But you all smell like thresher urine.
但你们闻起来都像脱粒机尿一样。
And your wanted poster just went up all over town.
你的通缉令已经传遍了全城。
So, I suggest that you all settle in and clean up.
因此，我建议你们都安顿下来并清理干净。
Now, the electroshower is right over there.
现在，电淋浴器就在那里。
Ooh, shower.
噢，淋浴。
Hey, kids, we're out of here. Let's go.
嘿，孩子们，我们要走了。走吧。
Lilith? Hey, I get it. There's history here.
莉莉丝？嘿，我明白了。这里面有历史。
I don't even need to know what it is.
我甚至不需要知道它是什么。
The point is that she's right.
关键是她是对的。
If there's a poster of me, that means there's one of you.
如果有我的海报，那就意味着那里也有你。
They're looking for all of us.
他们正在寻找我们所有人。
I hate to say it, but we don't have a choice.
我不想这么说，但我们别无选择。
We gotta sit tight.
我们必须稳住。
Lilith, we don't have a choice.
莉莉丝，我们别无选择。
What is happening, Tannis?
发生什么事了，坦尼斯？
-Electroshower. - Wait.
-电动淋浴器。-等一下。
Wait, guys.
等一下，伙计们。
-Time to shower. - Claptrap.
-该洗澡了。- 废话。
♪ It's time for showering Showering, time for some... ♪
♪ 该洗澡了 洗澡，该做点什么了…… ♪
That's not... No.
那不是…不。
Claptrap.
废话。
Rebooting.
正在重新启动。
Everybody, just settle down, please.
请大家安静下来。
Settle down.
安家。
Hey, hey! Settle down.
嘿，嘿！冷静下来。
Square root of 929,000...
929,000 的平方根......
I am basing my assumption that you're upset
我假设你很沮丧
on your body language.
你的肢体语言。
Perceptive as ever, I see.
我看，还是一如既往的敏锐。
Because of your mother?
因为你妈妈？
Uh, no, because of you.
呃，不，是因为你。
She trusted you...
她信任你……
to take care of me.
照顾我。
But you ran back here
但你跑回这里
to chase after that mystical Eridian vault bullshit.
去追寻那个神秘的 Eridian 金库废话。
I left you with tradespeople.
我把你留给了商人。
Oh.
哦。
Yes. You mean the murderers and thieves
是的。你指的是凶手和小偷
on the mining ship.
在采矿船上。
It's what your mother wanted.
这正是你母亲想要的。
She wanted me to learn how to kill
她想让我学会如何杀人
by the age of 10?
到 10 岁为止？
How to survive.
如何生存。
I had to come back here to finish her work.
我必须回到这里完成她的工作。
She believed the Eridian vault
她相信伊瑞迪安宝库
had the power to change things for the better and...
有能力让事情变得更好并且......
She traded her daughter for a waste of time.
她用女儿换来了浪费的时间。
Go back inside.
回到屋里去。
It's not safe.
这不安全。
I can look after myself.
我能照顾好自己。
Told you I'm special.
告诉你我很特别。
Aren't we all?
我们不都是这样吗？
Yeah.
是的。
They made me that way.
他们把我变成这个样子。
Made you?
造诣了你吗？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Your father is Deukalian Atlas,
你的父亲是德卡利安·阿特拉斯，
isn't he?
不是吗？
Yes and no.
是也不是。
Not a "yes or no" question.
不是一个“是或否”的问题。
He's...
他是…
my...
我的...
creator.
创建者。
Atlas is bananapants obsessed with the vault.
阿特拉斯 (Atlas) 非常痴迷于金库。
He says only a daughter of Eridia can open it.
他说只有埃利迪亚的女儿才能打开它。
He found a piece of the vault key,
他找到了保险库钥匙的碎片，
and on that piece
在那件作品上
was a tiny bit...
有一点点……
of blood.
血液。
Eridian blood.
伊瑞德之血。
He cloned an Eridian.
他克隆了一个伊瑞德人。
And guess who that Eridian is?
猜猜那个 Eridian 是谁？
Hmm. Is her name Tina?
嗯。她叫蒂娜吗？
Boom.
繁荣。
But it's all good.
但一切都很好。
I don't care I grew up in a lab.
我不在乎我是在实验室长大的。
I never wanted a mother or a father.
我从来不想要母亲或父亲。
He created you to open a vault.
他创造你是为了打开金库。
God, what an asshole.
天啊，真是个混蛋。
That's an understatement.
这还只是轻描淡写。
He'll use whatever technology's inside
他会利用里面的任何技术
and make superweapons.
并制造超级武器。
The dude's got major issues.
这家伙有大问题了。
I'm just a product to Atlas.
对 Atlas 来说我只是一个产品。
If he gets me,
如果他抓住我，
he's gonna make me open the vault.
他要让我打开保险库。
Then he's just gonna lock me up into another secret lab
然后他就会把我关进另一个秘密实验室
and do more experiments.
并做更多的实验。
And if you saw the things they did
如果你看到他们所做的事情
to the other clones...
对于其他克隆人来说......
He's not gonna find you.
他不会找到你的。
Yo! Whassup?
哟！怎么了？
Yeah!
是的！
Hey, there, sugar chips.
嘿，那儿有糖片。
You need a firmware update?
您需要固件更新吗？
Piss off, short stuff.
滚开，矮个子。
Someone needs an oil change.
有人需要换油。
My daddy always had a saying.
我爸爸总是有一句话。
Never trust a man who can't hold his liquor.
永远不要相信一个不能喝酒的男人。
She tased me, all right?
她电击了我，好吗？
I love alcohol.
我喜欢喝酒。
I can be wild.
我可以很狂野。
As for that little girl,
至于那个小女孩，
you don't think the second I saw her,
你不觉得当我看到她时，
I wouldn't hand her right over to you
我不会把她交给你
just to get rid of you?
只是为了摆脱你？
I admire the fight,
我钦佩这场斗争，
but let me take you through what happens next.
但让我告诉你接下来会发生什么。
Spare parts! We seal the city...
备用件！我们封锁这座城市……
Anyone got spare parts that I can use?
谁有我可以使用的备用零件？
Uh-oh.
哎呀。
Hey, hey, that's his robot.
嘿，嘿，那是他的机器人。
It's an old CL4P...
这是一个旧的 CL4P...
Excuse me. Coming through.
不好意思，我进来了。
Got a computer virus. Highly contagious.
感染了计算机病毒。传染性极强。
Clear the street!
清理街道！
You, down on the ground.
你，倒在地上。
Move, move, move!
动起来，动起来，动起来！
Now that we have Tina and the first key,
现在我们有了蒂娜和第一把钥匙，
I wanna show you this.
我想给你看这个。
This is a mining journal left behind
这是一本被遗留下来的采矿日志
by a corporate bureaucrat.
由企业官僚制定。
He cataloged everything the miners brought in,
他对矿工带回来的所有东西进行了分类，
most of it useless.
大部分都是无用的。
But on this page...
但在此页面上...
Another key.
另一把钥匙。
He thought it was a useless piece of Eridian pottery.
他认为这只是一块无用的伊瑞德陶器。
He had no clue they'd found a vault key.
他根本不知道他们找到了保险库钥匙。
That makes two of three.
这就等于三之二。
So, if this is the second key,
所以，如果这是第二把钥匙，
why don't you already have it?
为什么你还没有它？
Because the mine is in Caustic Caverns.
因为矿井位于 Caustic Caverns。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Danger! Red alert!
危险！红色警报！
People, we need to move! The soldiers, they're coming!
大家，我们要行动！士兵们来了！
They have guns! They're shooting!
他们有枪！他们正在射击！
- They're firing! - Clappy, slow your roll.
- 他们开火了！ - 克拉皮，放慢速度。
What is the dealio?
这是什么交易？
The soldier woman who really hates Roland,
真正讨厌罗兰的女兵，
which suggests the two of them had some...
这表明他们两个有一些……
- Come on, get to the point. - She was at the bar
- 来吧，说重点。- 她在酒吧
interrogating Moxxi and your friend Larry...
审问 Moxxi 和你的朋友 Larry……
Was that his name?
那是他的名字吗？
Seemed like a decent roommate.
看起来像是一个不错的室友。
Did they see you?
他们看到你了吗？
Do you promise not to be angry if I say yes?
如果我答应了，你能保证不会生气吗？
Lance units, block all exits.
长矛部队，封锁所有出口。
No one leaves.
没有人离开。
Get this thing out of here.
把这个东西拿走。
Masks off.
摘掉面具。
Of course, Commander.
当然了，指挥官。
Of course. Hey!
当然。嘿！
Double-perched custom Blaster with ionized projectiles.
双栖定制爆能枪，配备电离射弹。
That'll outpace any bone shredder on Pandora.
这将超过潘多拉上的任何碎骨机。
You wanna trade?
你想交易吗？
I'll give you special price, huh?
我可以给你优惠价，嗯？
Sanctuary is now on lockdown.
避难所目前已被封锁。
No one goes anywhere until we find that robot.
在我们找到那个机器人之前，谁也不许去任何地方。
Is there any way out of here that doesn't involve garbage?
有没有什么办法可以离开这里而不产生垃圾？
Um...
一...
No.
不。
What?
什么？
Did you guys wanna use it?
你们想用它吗？
The entrance is underneath all of that debris.
入口就在那些碎片下面。
Under there.
在那下面。
Whoo! Look what I got!
哇哦！看看我得到了什么！
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
嘿！哇，哇，哇。
Open it.
打开它。
Hello.
你好。
Would you look at that? A ladder.
你能看看那个吗？一个梯子。
Unfortunately, my design doesn't facilitate
不幸的是，我的设计不利于
this type of vertical travel.
这种垂直旅行。
Drats.
德拉茨。
Guess I'll just...
我想我只是...
Well...
出色地...
- Destiny awaits. -I'm fine!
- 命运在等待。 - 我很好！
Mm! Meat soup.
嗯！肉汤。
Chemical waste from the mining equipment.
来自采矿设备的化学废物。
It's corrosive enough to dissolve almost anything
它的腐蚀性足以溶解几乎所有的东西
except the natural crystals in this cavern.
除了这个洞穴中的天然水晶。
How are we gonna get through this?
我们怎样才能渡过难关？
Well, it's not gonna be that way.
嗯，事实不会是那样的。
Looks like we gotta take the high road.
看来我们得走高速公路了。
Krieg.
战争。
Let's see if we can grab this here.
让我们看看是否可以在这里抓住它。
Luckily, my wheel's too large,
幸运的是我的轮子太大了，
so I'll just watch you all melt
所以我只能看着你们融化
from a safe and reasonable distance.
保持安全且合理的距离。
You are small enough to get in there.
你够小，可以进入那里。
Head through the tunnel,
穿过隧道，
locate the main access control panel and then unlock
找到主访问控制面板，然后解锁
- the door at the end. -Can do!
- 尽头的门。- 可以做到！
- Quietly. -No problem.
- 安静点。- 没问题。
I wouldn't want anything bad to happen to each one of you
我不希望你们每个人都遭遇任何不幸
in the most horrifying way possible.
以最恐怖的方式。
All right, I'll go first.
好，我先走了。
- I got this. - No, I got it.
- 我明白了。 - 不，我明白了。
- I got it. -Tina!
- 我明白了。-蒂娜！
Coming through! Hey, hey.
来了！嘿，嘿。
Relax.
放松。
I'm the lightest.
我是最轻的。
- Tina! - Hey!
- 蒂娜！- 嘿！
Ladies first.
女士优先。
Don't mind if I do.
如果我这么做的话，别介意。
- You all right? - Mm-hmm.
- 你还好吗？ - 嗯。
Be careful.
当心。
Guys.
伙计们。
Look.
看。
Hope blooms in the strangest places.
希望在最奇怪的地方绽放。
It's kind of pretty.
有点漂亮。
Mission accomplished!
任务完成！
The door is unlocked.
门没有锁。
♪ Who's the best? I'm the best ♪
♪ 谁最棒？ 我最棒 ♪
♪ Give me a job I pass the test ♪
♪ 给我一份工作 我通过了考试 ♪
Can't take him anywhere.
不能带他去任何地方。
Well?
出色地？
You're welcome.
不客气。
Impossible to please.
不可能令人满意。
Scream showers.
尖叫淋浴。
It's Bloodshots.
是 Bloodshots。
Yeah, their symbols are everywhere.
是的，他们的符号无处不在。
These are the Psychos other psychos are afraid of.
这些是其他精神病患者所害怕的精神病患者。
They're probably still here.
他们可能还在这里。
- Let's go find out. -  No bombs.
- 我们去看看吧。 - 没有炸弹。
I'll be surgical.
我会进行手术。
There's only one of you in the world...
这世上只有一个你……
and you're special.
你很特别。
You guys sit tight. Wait for us to come back.
你们坐稳，等我们回来。
Come on, Lil.
来吧，莉尔。
Dealt with Bloodshots before?
以前处理过 Bloodshots 吗？
Once.
一次。
How'd you make it out?
你是怎么摆脱的？
Kind words and hugs?
亲切的话语和拥抱？
I don't know what it is that happens to 'em
我不知道他们发生了什么事
when they're down here
当他们在这里的时候
but it's like they get hit with an extra dose of crazy.
但他们就像被额外剂量的疯狂击中了一样。
Strip the flesh, salt the wound!
剥去肉体，在伤口上撒盐！
- There's too many to shoot. - Or blow up?
- 数量太多，无法射击。 - 或者炸毁？
Well, we can't really blend in.
嗯，我们确实没法融入其中。
We don't look anything like them.
我们看起来和他们一点都不像。
Except you, handsome.
除了你，帅哥。
Thank you!
谢谢你！
Well, according to my calculations,
根据我的计算，
the odds of a successful stealth operation
秘密行动成功的几率
in this scenario is...
在这种情况下是……
0%? Wow!
0%？哇！
You never see that!
你绝对没见过这样的情况！
Well, I guess that's it then. Back to the truck, right?
好吧，我想就这样了。回到卡车上，对吧？
Did you factor in a distraction?
您是否考虑过干扰因素？
Of course.
当然。
I analyzed 16 million versions
我分析了1600万个版本
where one of you creates a distraction.
你们其中一人造成了干扰。
Total failure.
彻底失败。
No, not one of us.
不，我们中没有一个人。
Wait, who else is...?
等一下，还有谁……？
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Coming through.
正在通过。
Hi, there.
你好呀。
How you doing?
你好吗？
Just a little nervous laughter to crack the ice.
只需一点紧张的笑声就能打破僵局。
Shiny!
闪亮的！
Just rolling through town
只是穿过城镇
looking for a good time.
寻找美好时光。
Ladies and gentlemen!
女士们，先生们！
Your attention, please.
请注意。
I am here because I want to be
我来这里是因为我想
and not for a more justifiable reason
而不是出于更正当的理由
like trying to be a distraction.
就像试图分散注意力一样。
Even though it makes no sense
尽管这毫无意义
for me to say what I'm about to say,
让我说出我想说的话，
and even though anyone rational
即使任何理性的人
would suspect it was just part of a crude plan,
会怀疑这只是一个粗略计划的一部分，
I have decided
我决定了
entirely on my own to say the following.
以下内容完全由我个人撰写。
Y'all bitches need to eat your own butts
你们这些婊子应该吃自己的屁股
with your poopy-mouth...
用你的屎嘴……
...ass-faces until you die from loser poisoning
...直到你死于失败者毒害
like the stupid pus-crotches that you is.
就像你这个愚蠢的脓包一样。
Was that too much? It was too much, wasn't it?
是不是太多了？是不是太多了？
What took it over the edge?
是什么让它走向了绝境？
Was it the "poopy-mouth ass-faces"?
是“满嘴屎的屁股脸”吗？
Stairs. Come on!
楼梯。来吧！
Not in the undercarriage!
不在底盘里！
My programming...
我的编程...
Oh, that's gonna leave a mark.
噢，那会留下痕迹的。
Son of a... You got me!
你这个……你成功抓住我了！
Okay, I'm dead. How about that?
好吧，我死了。那怎么样？
Is he going to be all right?
他会没事吗？
Excellent plan.
非常好的计划。
Who would have guessed they'd shoot me, right?
谁会想到他们会向我开枪呢，对吧？
Well, we survived.
好吧，我们活了下来。
So much for your 0%.
您的 0% 就这么多。
You're not out yet.
你还没出去。
I think the key's in here.
我想钥匙就在这里。
Sweet.
甜的。
So, the key is in one of these crates.
所以，钥匙就在其中一个板条箱里。
One of these
其中之一
kabillion crates.
数以亿计的板条箱。
Yeah, this is gonna take a minute.
是的，这需要一点时间。
Four days if you work around the clock
如果你全天候工作，则需要四天时间
which you can't,
但你做不到，
because your bodies require rest every 16 hours.
因为你的身体每16小时就需要休息一次。
Lazy!
懒惰的！
Not if those psycho Raiders find us first.
如果那些疯狂的袭击者先发现我们的话就不会了。
Those are Bloodshots.
那些是血丝。
Raiders live above. Not down here.
袭击者住在上面。不住在下面。
There are no Raiders down here.
这里没有袭击者。
Tannis, nobody's talking about Raiders.
坦尼斯，没人谈论突击者队。
What's the big deal about Raiders?
袭击者队有何大不了？
I know, but you brought up Raiders.
我知道，但是你提到了突袭者队。
How about we forget about it?
咱们就忘掉这件事怎么样？
Am I missing something here?
我这里遗漏了什么吗？
But I don't understand.
但我不明白。
Forget about the Raiders!
忘掉突袭者吧！
Just forget about it.
忘掉它吧。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I understand...
我明白...
- Bloodshots are down here. - You keep bringing up Raiders.
- Bloodshots 就在这里。 - 你一直在提起袭击者。
- Tannis, I swear to God... -I found it.
— 坦尼斯，我向上帝发誓... — 我找到了。
- What? -The second key.
—什么？—第二把钥匙。
How... How did...?
怎么...怎么会...?
I don't know. Just lucky, I guess.
我不知道。我猜只是运气好。
Yeah, we'll see how lucky you are.
是的，我们看看你有多幸运。
We still gotta get out of here.
我们还是得离开这里。
There's an exit portal this way.
这边有一个出口。
Come on.
快点。
Shh!
嘘！
What's that?
那是什么？
What? I'm expelling the excess lead.
啥？我在排出多余的铅。
Big bullet. Big bullet coming. There we go.
大子弹。大子弹来了。我们走了。
Can't you do this another time?
你不能再做一次吗？
This has to happen now.
这必须立即发生。
Don't judge me.
别评判我。
What? How is this funny?
啥？这有什么好笑的？
You keep it down.
你小声点。
Do I judge you when you blast out a loaf?
当你烤出一块面包时我会评判你吗？
- We don't wanna attract... -Look out!
- 我们不想吸引... - 小心！
A little help?
有一点帮助吗？
Incoming!
来啦！
Go, go! Okay, going now!
走吧，走吧！好，现在就走！
Tannis!
坦尼斯！
Thank you.
谢谢。
On your left!
在你的左边！
Wow!
哇！
Come here, girlie!
过来吧，姑娘！
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I needed a gun.
我需要一把枪。
So you ask for it, Tannis. Ask!
所以你自找的，坦尼斯。问吧！
Move!
移动！
That way!
这样！
We've got this, guys!
伙计们，我们成功了！
There's nothing we can't do!
没有我们做不到的事！
Stairs!
楼梯！
Krieg, help me! I'm not...
克里格，救救我！我没有……
Go, go!
走吧，走吧！
Lilith, I got you!
莉莉丝，我抓到你了！
Go!
去！
Roland!
罗兰！
Watch out!
小心！
Go, go!
走吧，走吧！
Time to go.
该走了。
I'm sure we're past the hard part.
我确信我们已经渡过了困难时期。
Okay.
好的。
Go, go, go! We gotta move!
快走，快走！我们得走了！
Let go of me! Tina!
放开我！蒂娜！
Lilith! Hello!
莉莉丝！你好！
Follow me this way.
跟我来这边走。
I have a tremendous sense of direction.
我有很强的方向感。
Oh, God!
噢，天哪！
Help me!
帮我！
Krieg, spin me!
战争，旋转我！
I found it! I found it!
我找到了！我找到了！
There's an elevator!
有电梯！
Follow me. This way. Come on.
跟我来。这边走。来吧。
- Roland! -Clappy, go! Go! Go!
- 罗兰！- 克拉皮，快走！快走！快走！
Lilith! Don't leave me behind again!
莉莉丝！别再丢下我了！
There's a service elevator this way!
这边有服务电梯！
It's up here.
它在这儿。
- This way. Oh, no. -Go! Go, go, go!
- 这边走。哦，不。-走！走，走，走！
Shit!
拉屎！
This is gonna take some time. Hold this.
这得花点时间。稍等一下。
Claptrap!
废话！
I need help!
我需要帮助！
Uh, in front of everyone?
呃，当着大家的面？
Yes! Look away!
是啊！别往那边看！
Look away! I command you!
别往那边看！我命令你！
Krieg, we got company.
克里格，我们有同伴了。
It's time to bleed!
流血的时间到了！
- Come on! - I am trying!
- 来吧！- 我正在努力！
Krieg, wait!
战争，等等！
Krieg!
战争！
It's not working.
它不起作用。
Aren't you supposed to be smart?
你不是应该很聪明吗？
I'll turn you into a meat bicycle!
我要把你变成肉自行车！
Another victim!
又有一名受害者！
Thanks, kid.
谢谢，孩子。
Tannis!
坦尼斯！
- How we doing? -I don't have it!
- 我们怎么样了？ - 我没有！
Come here, give me a kiss!
过来，亲我一下！
Krieg! Pull back!
战争！拉回来！
Go! Go!
走吧！走吧！
I regret everything!
我对一切都感到后悔！
Come on!
快点！
-We gotta go. - It's not working.
-我们得走了。-它不起作用。
Go, Tannis.
走吧，坦尼斯。
We have another wiring problem.
我们遇到了另一个接线问题。
Baby!
婴儿！
Shit.
拉屎。
- Roland, what are you doing? -Fixing it.
- 罗兰，你在做什么？- 修理它。
- Get back here! -Hey.
- 回来！- 嘿。
No. Please don't.
不，请不要这样做。
- Roland! - Hey, Tina.
- 罗兰！ - 嘿，蒂娜。
I'll meet you at the vault.
我将在保险库与你见面。
I promise.
我保证。
Tannis.
坦尼斯。
- Hit it! - Okay, hitting!
- 击中！ - 好，击中！
Roland!
罗兰！
All right, Bob.
好的，鲍勃。
You ready to kick some ass?
你准备好大干一场了吗？
I knew you'd say that.
我就知道你会这么说。
The brakes are out! We are not slowing down!
刹车失灵了！我们不会减速！
We are not gonna make it!
我们不会成功的！
Teleportation.
瞬间移动。
I can move stuff with my mind, y'all.
我可以用我的思想来移动东西，你们。
We're not dead?
我们还没死？
I'm still enslaved? Drats.
我还被奴役着？糟糕。
Chutney vomit queen. Ew! Yuck!
酸辣酱呕吐女王。呸！真恶心！
I think the teleportation has made her quite ill.
我认为这次瞬间移动让她病得很重。
How did you do that?
你是怎么做到的？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Just kind of happened.
就这样发生了。
Hey, Roland's gonna be okay, right?
嘿，罗兰会没事的，对吧？
He's an elite soldier.
他是一名精锐士兵。
If anyone can get out of that, it's him.
如果有人能摆脱这种困境，那就是他。
Where are we?
我们在哪里？
I can't get a read on ECHOnet.
我无法读取 ECHOnet 上的内容。
But it looks like we're in an old mine.
但看起来我们是在一个旧矿井里。
Maybe we find some shelter inside.
也许我们可以在里面找到一些庇护所。
I've combined the keys.
我已将钥匙组合起来。
Look.
看。
What's that? Some kind of a map?
那是什么？是地图吗？
Incredible, isn't it?
难以置信，不是吗？
It isn't just a key.
它不仅仅是一把钥匙。
And right there...
就在那里...
The vault?
金库？
It is a shame
真可惜
your mother is not here to see this.
你的妈妈没有在这里看到这一切。
It was there the whole time.
它一直在那里。
Apparently.
显然。
I've seen that before somewhere.
我以前在某个地方见过这个。
Firehawk.
火鹰。
Eridian goddess, protector of the planet.
伊瑞德女神，星球的保护者。
Well, it's all a bit pointless without the third piece.
好吧，如果没有第三件，这一切都毫无意义了。
Oh, well, we have it.
噢，好的，我们有了。
She's the key.
她就是关键。
The elevator confirmed it.
电梯证实了这一点。
That was a phasewalk.
那是一次阶段性行走。
Only an Eridian could do that.
只有伊瑞德人才能做到这一点。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
If she's a piece of the key,
如果她是钥匙的一部分，
what happens when she opens it?
当她打开它时会发生什么？
I assumed you knew.
我以为你知道。
Did your mother never tell you?
你妈妈从来没有告诉过你吗？
I was eight. I can barely remember her face.
我当时八岁。我几乎记不起她的脸了。
When the daughter of Eridia places the key,
当埃利迪亚的女儿把钥匙放进去时，
the pieces are consumed and the vault opens.
碎片被消耗后保险库就会打开。
Now, I don't necessarily believe that means kill her.
现在，我不一定相信这意味着杀死她。
But you're prepared to take that risk.
但您已准备好承担这个风险。
Well, we have no choice.
好吧，我们别无选择。
Either we take her
我们要么带她去
or Atlas does.
或者 Atlas 也可以。
There is no salvation without sacrifice.
没有牺牲就没有救赎。
Worst orgy ever.
史上最糟糕的群交。
Rest in peace, Bob.
安息吧，鲍勃。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Whoa. Sorry.
哇哦。抱歉。
I thought for a moment there you had rigor mortis.
我一时还以为你是尸僵了。
It was a really nice moment.
那真是一个美好的时刻。
I'll treasure it always.
我会永远珍惜它。
Also, I scavenged the final parts I needed
此外，我还找到了我需要的最后零件
from a dead transformer,
来自一个坏掉的变压器，
and fixed the thing you so recklessly destroyed.
并修复了被你鲁莽毁坏的东西。
You didn't press this, did you?
您没有按这个吧？
I did not.
我没有。
I can crush it again if you'd like.
如果你愿意的话我可以再次将其粉碎。
Oh, "Thank you, Claptrap. You're indispensable."
哦，“谢谢你，Claptrap。你太重要了。”
Thank you, Lilith. Your praise warms my soul.
谢谢你，莉莉丝。你的赞美温暖了我的心灵。
Lilith.
莉莉丝。
Have you broken the beacon I gave you?
你弄坏了我给你的信标吗？
Ah, this thing was junk the whole time.
啊，这东西一直都是垃圾。
Not at all.
一点也不。
It was a highly accurate tracking device
这是一个高度精确的跟踪装置
that has led me right to you and Tina.
这让我直接认识了你和蒂娜。
Now, I was beginning to think
现在我开始思考
that she would elude me forever.
她将永远躲避我。
She's smart.
她很聪明。
She is mine.
她是我的。
And the Crimson Lance
还有赤红之枪
are on their way to collect her now.
正在去接她的路上。
If you come after her, I'll destroy the key.
如果你来追她，我就会毁掉钥匙。
No, you won't.
不，你不会的。
Because if you did,
因为如果你这么做了，
then I would have to kill
那么我就得杀了
the rest of that heroic band of vault hunters
其余的英雄猎人
she's been slumming around with.
她一直在和贫民窟的人在一起。
And I promise you, Lilith,
我向你保证，莉莉丝，
they won't be quick deaths.
他们不会很快死去。
Good.
好的。
Glad to see you making
很高兴看到你
the smart choice for once.
一次明智的选择。
And when this is over,
当这一切结束后，
you'll be paid what we agreed on.
您将获得我们约定的报酬。
Thank you, Lilith.
谢谢你，莉莉丝。
Oh.
哦。
Tina, look, I know how this must look, but...
蒂娜，你看，我知道这看起来怎么样，但是......
I'm the only one who can open the vault.
我是唯一一个可以打开保险库的人。
And I'm gonna use whatever is inside to kill him.
我要用里面的东西杀死他。
Too bad you won't be around to see it.
可惜您没能亲眼见证这一切。
- Wait. - Enjoy your freedom.
- 等一下。- 享受你的自由。
Tina. Tina, no!
蒂娜。蒂娜，不！
I'm dancing because...
我跳舞是因为...
you're alive.
你还活着。
Not because I thought you were dead.
并不是因为我以为你已经死了。
Heartwarming.
令人暖心。
Where are the others?
其他人在哪儿？
They found a truck in the village and left.
他们在村子里找到一辆卡车然后离开。
Without me.
没有我。
What village?
哪个村子？
This must have been one of the original
这肯定是原创的
Pandoran settlements.
潘多拉定居点。
How quaint.
多么古雅啊。
I know this place.
我知道这个地方。
Come on. Come on. Leave it.
来吧，来吧，别再说了。
Come on, sweetie.
来吧，亲爱的。
Hurry, give me Lilith!
快把莉莉丝给我！
Come on! Come on!
加油！加油！
Remember I will always love you!
记住我会永远爱你！
Mama!
妈妈！
No!
不！
Hey, where are you going?
嘿，你要去哪儿？
Lilith.
莉莉丝。
Lilith!
莉莉丝！
Is this your home?
这是你的家吗？
Yeah.
是的。
I used to live here once.
我曾经住在这里。
This place is...
这个地方是...
reminiscent of something deep in my files.
让我回想起文件深处的一些东西。
That drawing...
那幅画……
I feel strange.
我感觉很奇怪。
Lilith.
莉莉丝。
Mom?
妈妈？
If you're seeing this...
如果您看到这个...
I'm afraid I didn't make it.
我恐怕没能成功。
I'm so sorry that I sent you away.
我很抱歉把你送走了。
I didn't want to.
我不想。
But as soon as I realized
但我很快就意识到
what you are,
你是什​​么，
what you might become...
你可能会成为什么……
I knew you'd never be safe here on Pandora.
我知道在潘多拉星球上你永远不会安全。
But if you ever return,
但如果你回来的话，
I've made sure that Claptrap will find you,
我确信 Claptrap 会找到你，
help you understand...
帮助你理解...
your destiny.
你的命运。
Lilith, I love you.
莉莉丝，我爱你。
I wish...
我希望……
I could hold you one last time.
我可以最后一次拥抱你。
Tina!
蒂娜！
Whoa. That was weird.
哇哦。这太奇怪了。
I blacked out.
我昏了过去。
Did something important happen?
是不是发生什么重要的事情了？
It's saying it's here.
它说它就在这里。
All I'm seeing is some holes.
我看到的只是一些洞。
Are you sure this is it?
你确定就是这个吗？
I don't know. It's somewhere.
我不知道。它在某个地方。
Okay, what does it look like?
好的，它看起来像什么？
Big. It's an arch.
很大。是拱门。
It's here somewhere. I know it's here.
它就在这儿的某个地方。我知道它就在这儿。
How do you know it's here?
你怎么知道它在这里？
Because I'm feeling emotion.
因为我感受到情感。
Can you be more specific?
你能更具体一点吗？
- Thing of power! - Not right now, Krieg. Please.
- 力量！- 现在不行，克里格。求你了。
- Okay, I get it... - But that means something!
- 好的，我明白了... - 但这意味着什么！
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
I'm not following.
我没有关注。
Krieg, you genius. You found it!
克里格，你真是个天才。你找到了！
I have to warn you, this might kill you.
我得警告你，这可能会要了你的命。
Me?
我？
Nah, kid. I'm the special one.
不，孩子。我才是特别的一个。
Whatever this is, it's gonna make me invincible.
无论这是什么，它都会让我变得无敌。
What just happened?
刚才发生了什么？
I'm the special one. It should do something.
我是特别的一个。它应该做点什么。
Apparently not.
显然不是。
Well done, Tina.
干得好，蒂娜。
Well done.
做得好。
Amazing effort.
令人惊奇的努力。
You survived the worst planet in the galaxy.
你在银河系最糟糕的星球上幸存了下来。
You found the key and the vault itself.
你找到了钥匙和保险库本身。
You've made your father so proud.
你让你的父亲感到非常骄傲。
Commander Knoxx,
诺克斯指挥官，
I need her nervous system intact.
我需要她的神经系统完好无损。
Keep the organs on ice.
将器官放在冰上。
Perhaps we'll have better luck with the next clone.
也许下一个克隆人会给我们带来更好的运气。
Hey, asshole.
嘿，混蛋。
That was quite an entrance, Roland.
罗兰，你的出场可真是精彩啊。
You miss me?
你想念我？
You might have saved the day if it wasn't for...
如果不是因为……你也许已经挽救了局面。
my Atlas auto shield.
我的 Atlas 汽车防护罩。
Kill them all.
把他们全部杀掉。
Hold your fire.
不要开火。
That's an order.
这是命令。
You heard the commander.
您听到了指挥官的话。
Weapons down.
武器放下。
Roland, you were right.
罗兰，你说得对。
I should've...
我应该...
No!
不！
Any other objections?
还有其他异议吗？
Just one!
仅一个！
That you continue breathing.
你继续呼吸。
But I'll allow it
但我会允许
if you let my friends go in peace.
如果你能让我的朋友平安地离去。
And tell me, Lilith,
告诉我，莉莉丝，
just why would I do that?
我为什么要这么做？
Because I'm the daughter of Eridia.
因为我是埃利迪亚的女儿。
I've seen that before somewhere.
我以前在某个地方见过这个。
Firehawk.
火鹰。
Eridian goddess.
伊瑞迪安女神。
It's your planet, Lilith.
这是你的星球，莉莉丝。
You have to protect it.
你必须保护它。
Mama loved you.
妈妈爱你。
She always told me how special you were.
她总是告诉我你有多特别。
I found it.
我找到了。
How did...? I don't know.
怎么会......？ 我不知道。
Just lucky, I guess.
我想，只是运气好而已。
Daughter of Eridia, baby!
埃利迪亚的女儿，宝贝！
Bet you didn't see that coming!
我敢打赌你没想到这一点！
But...
但...
But I'm the special one.
但我却是特别的一个。
Oh, you are.
噢，是的。
Just not the way you thought.
只是和你想像的不一样。
I open the vault...
我打开保险库……
the girl goes free.
女孩自由了。
You open the vault
你打开保险库
and you all go free.
你们都可以自由了。
You have my word.
我向你保证。
I just figured it out.
我刚刚明白了。
Your mother gave you to me
你妈妈把你给了我
to take you away from here,
带你离开这里，
so you would never have to open that vault.
所以你就不需要打开那个保险库。
Well, that worked out great.
嗯，结果非常好。
I have to open it.
我必须打开它。
No salvation without sacrifice.
没有牺牲就没有救赎。
Remember?
记住？
But you can't.
但你不能。
You can't.
你不能。
It's fine.
没有什么。
You're safe.
你很安全。
And, Tina,
蒂娜，
memories are more powerful
记忆更加强大
than anything Atlas could ever create.
比 Atlas 所能创造的任何东西都要多。
Now, you got one of me.
现在，你得到我的一个了。
Yes.
是的。
Tannis, what's happening?
坦尼斯，发生什么事了？
The Eridians have delivered us
伊瑞德人拯救了我们
a champion.
冠军。
The legends were true.
传说是真的。
She's the Firehawk.
她是火鹰。
Lilith, can you hear me?
莉莉丝，你能听到我的声音吗？
Take me into the vault.
带我进金库。
If you won't, I'm going to have to hurt your friends.
如果你不这样做，我就要伤害你的朋友了。
Pull me up!
拉我上去！
Lilith, help!
莉莉丝，救命！
Make it rain, Tina!
让雨下吧，蒂娜！
Attack!
攻击！
Are you guys shooting?
你们在射击吗？
I'm sorry, I didn't feel a thing.
抱歉，我什么也没感觉到。
You get a bullet.
你中枪了。你中枪了。
Run, run.
跑，跑。
Interplanetary ninja assassin mode activated.
星际忍者刺客模式已激活。
Step aside, bitches.
让开，贱人。
Lilith. Lilith!
莉莉丝。莉莉丝！
No!
不！
Lilith, can you hear me?
莉莉丝，你能听到我的声音吗？
Well, it was fun while it lasted.
好吧，只要它持续下去，就很有趣。
Lilith. Come on, Lilith.
莉莉丝。来吧，莉莉丝。
Lilith.
莉莉丝。
Please wake up.
请你醒醒。
Tannis, run.
坦尼斯，快跑。
Nobody kills me but me!
除了我自己没人能杀我！
Everybody, run!
大家快跑！
Go! Move, move!
快走！快走！
Shit!
拉屎！
Tannis, you're alive.
坦尼斯，你还活着。
I'm alive!
我还活着！
This guy, not so much.
这家伙，不太一样。
A siren.
警报器响了。
Tina!
蒂娜！
Tannis, where's Tina?
坦尼斯，蒂娜在哪儿？
Lilith!
莉莉丝！
I warned you not to disappoint me.
我警告过你不要让我失望。
Take me to the vault now.
现在带我去金库。
Well, shit.
好吧，该死。
Let go of me!
放开我！
Keep struggling and I'll kill you.
继续挣扎的话我就杀了你。
Lilith!
莉莉丝！
Lilith, show yourself!
莉莉丝，展现你自己吧！
Show yourself or I kill her!
现身吧，不然我就杀了她！
I'll do it!
我会做到的！
Believe me.
相信我。
Oh, I believe you.
噢，我相信你。
Ah, Lilith.
啊，莉莉丝。
This is...
这是...
unbelievable.
难以置信。
So much more than I ever imagined.
比我想像的还要多。
The treasures of a race who once ruled the galaxies.
曾经统治过银河系的种族的宝藏。
Look.
看。
The power. Can you feel it?
那股力量。你能感受到吗？
Can you...
你可以吗...
Yeah, I can feel it.
是的，我能感觉到。
Honestly, it makes me a little sick.
说实话，这让我有点恶心。
You'll get used to it.
你会习惯的。
Yeah. You see...
是的。你看……
I have something that a man like you will never have.
我拥有一些像你这样的男人永远无法拥有的东西。
Enough.
足够的。
Lilith. Over here.
莉莉丝。在这儿。
Lose something?
丢了东西？
Tina!
蒂娜！
Ta-da.
哒哒。
Bye-bye.
再见。
No, Lilith.
不，莉莉丝。
- Lilith, please. -Don't worry.
- 莉莉丝，求你了。- 别担心。
You won't get lonely down here.
在这里你不会感到孤独。
No. No.
不不。
No, no, no. No!
不，不，不。不！
Lilith! Tina!
莉莉丝！蒂娜！
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
♪ It's like sugar ♪
♪ 就像糖一样 ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
♪ 太甜蜜了 ♪
Excuse me! Coming through.
不好意思！我进来了。
Make way for the hero!
为英雄让路！
Hey.
嘿。
You hear that?
你听见了吗？
What?
什么？
That I think is what peace sounds like.
我想，这就是和平的声音。
Enjoy it.
好好享受。
Let's make it last.
让我们让它持续下去。
I made you a little tea.
我给你泡了一点茶。
I thought you might be a little dehydrated.
我以为你可能有点脱水。
All right, guys. Let's, um...
好的，各位。让我们，嗯...
Let's join the party.
我们去参加聚会吧。
All right! Hooray!
好极了！太棒了！
Whoops. Premature celebration.
哎呀，庆祝得太早了。
That's never happened before.
这种事以前从来没有发生过。
You ready?
你准备好了吗？
We'll meet you there.
我们将在那里与你见面。
I got you.
我接到你了。
Come on, Krieg.
来吧，战争。
Time to go get drunk.
该去喝个酩酊大醉了。
Glorious meat fiesta.
盛大的肉食盛宴。
So...
所以...
Uh...
呃…
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
Come on.
快点。
Do the thing.
做那件事。
I'm a bit old, I think,
我觉得我有点老了，
to be setting myself on fire for your amusement.
为了取悦你们而把自己点燃。
You know you want to.
你知道你想要。
Let me tell you everything
让我告诉你一切
you need to know about Pandora.
您需要了解有关潘多拉的知识。
She's dangerous.
她很危险。
She's dirty.
她很脏。
And she's definitely a toxic waste dump.
她绝对是个有毒废物倾倒场。
But, she's my home.
但她是我的家。
What a show-off.
真是炫耀。
♪ If evil lays Its hands on me ♪
♪ 如果邪恶对我下手 ♪
♪ Shine a little light On my soul ♪
♪ 点亮一点光芒 照亮我的灵魂 ♪
♪ Show me things I cannot see ♪
♪ 让我看到我看不到的东西 ♪
♪ If evil lays Its hands on me ♪
♪ 如果邪恶对我下手 ♪
♪ Shine a little light On my soul ♪
♪ 点亮一点光芒 照亮我的灵魂 ♪
♪ I'm waiting, praying Patiently ♪
♪ 我等待着，耐心祈祷 ♪
♪ If evil lays Its hands on me ♪
♪ 如果邪恶对我下手 ♪
♪ Shine a little light On my soul ♪
♪ 点亮一点光芒 照亮我的灵魂 ♪
♪ Show me things I cannot see ♪
♪ 让我看到我看不到的东西 ♪
♪ If evil lays Its hands on me ♪
♪ 如果邪恶对我下手 ♪
♪ Shine a little light On my soul ♪
♪ 点亮一点光芒 照亮我的灵魂 ♪
♪ I'm waiting, praying Patiently ♪
♪ 我等待着，耐心祈祷 ♪
Woo-hoo! Check these moves.
哇喔！看看这些动作。
I come to dance, mofo.
我来跳舞啦，小子。
Twerk it. Work it out, now.
扭动身体。现在就锻炼。
Do the Claptrap. It's my...
做 Claptrap。这是我的……
Oh, hey! Hey, wait! No, no, no!
哦，嘿！嘿，等等！不，不，不！
What's goin' on here? No!
这是怎么回事？不！
It's my Easter egg!
这是我的复活节彩蛋！
Ah! You son of a...
啊！你这个混蛋……
Don't make me leave!
别让我离开！
Not when I'm giving the people what they want!
当我给予人们他们想要的东西时，情况并非如此！